I always wanted to do this, a video with all my Fernando Berlin boots.
I have four pair of them already and I think I didn't even show you all of them yet.
So, let's go!
Actually, I wanted to pair this bodysuit with nude ties, but it is too high cut in the legs here.
I thought the crotchet would go best with the bodysuit and I think that is my most favorite combination.
high cutout bodysuit and then high boots but as you would have seen the waistband
of the thighs I opted for black ones instead so you have to imagine this
being nude colored here these have been my second Fernando Bellin boots and it
is a bit hard to style them I give you that I've been asked a lot how do you
are your crotch highs because they don't look good with everything but yeah body
suits really short skirts for example as well or maybe just underwear depending
where you're headed since this outfit is very dark I want to give it some sparkle
and I have a collar here but I also have matching boot bands these are the red
ones yeah so I'm going to spice this one up I think it's a completely different
look with the zipper open the choker here and the Swarovski crystal boot bands
so you can have two looks in one with this outfit so to say I think this is
kind of a fetishy outfit but I mean with these crotch eye boots you're bound to
to stand out. Okay change of outfits and boots now.
Next pair of boots
this time with buckles and some silver
that's why I chose a belt
with silver elements and I paired it
with a mini skirt and a blouse
or is it a jacket? I don't know. So it's a two piece
with the corset in between. I think it's kind of like a rocky look like from rock
music not from stones. Anyway I've already worn this outfit last year at
the avant-garde itself for my live talk that's why I picked it again for this
video because I really like it. I love this floaty skirt here. So this is my
personal favorite kind of combination with these boots also compared to the
bodysuit before just like more of a skirt and shorter boots type
it's a catsuit and boots I have to say they are more comfortable than the other
ones simply because they don't have a heel it is what it is I've worn them to
my favorite bar for a night out to a trade fair for walking around the whole
day I have a video from that trade fair here and these are simply my favorite
favorite favorite vanara balloon boots because to be honest I like to live a comfy
life and to walk in flat boots I paired them with catsuit here and to add a
little something extra a belt because what would this channel be without a
catsuit in the video? No honestly I think these look great in combination with a
catsuit. Okay last outfit I'm going to switch to some high-heeled boots again
and the last outfit with the last pair of boots this time laser boots and these
These have been among the first FANANO Berlin boots I've ever tried.
Quite a while ago at a trade fair.
And I fell in love with them because they're really elegant and I just think this lacing
style is something really cool.
I paired it with a short four leather skirt and a bodysuit and I'm quite happy with this
combination. Let me check the mirror. Yeah. I have to put it down sometimes because it rides up.
There's a really fun way to lace these kind of boots. There is like one hand technique I
mastered by now I have to say and you can check out the clip or I have an even older video
with these boots or when I visited Ferdinand in his showroom so quite a
lot of Ferdinand Berlin stuff on my channel already so make sure to
subscribe otherwise we're going to miss videos if you want to support this
channel check out my patreon I have to say special thanks to George you know
why and yeah I think that was it for today and see you in the next video have
Have a good time. Bye!